import 'question.dart';

const List<Question> questions = [
  Question(
    question : '1. Who is the founder of facebook?',
    correctAnswerIndex : 1,
    options: [
      'a) Steve Jobs',
      'b) Mark Zuckerberg',
      'c) Bill Gates',
      'd) Elon Musk',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question : '2. What is the NEWEST iPhone?',
    correctAnswerIndex : 1,
    options: [
      'a) iPhone 14',
      'b) iPhone 15',
      'c) iPhone 16',
      'd) iPhone 17',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question : '3. What name of X before?',
    correctAnswerIndex : 2,
    options: [
      'a) Twich',
      'b) Twerk',
      'c) Twitter',
      'd) Twingle twingle little star',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question : '4. What is Youtube?',
    correctAnswerIndex : 3,
    options: [
      'a) Social media',
      'b) News',
      'c) Video games',
      'd) Video and Music',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question : '5. What is Razer logo look like?',
    correctAnswerIndex : 1,
    options: [
      'a) Snack',
      'b) Snake',
      'c) Chemicals',
      'd) Danger sign',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question : '6. What is answer of 1+1 in binary number?',
    correctAnswerIndex : 2,
    options: [
      'a) 2',
      'b) 1',
      'c) 10',
      'd) 11',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question : '7. What is mean of VS code?',
    correctAnswerIndex : 3,
    options: [
      'a) Vicual Studio code',
      'b) Vasco code',
      'c) Visal code',
      'd) Visual Studio code',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question : '8. What is answer of 20 % 4?',
    correctAnswerIndex : 0,
    options: [
      'a) 0',
      'b) 5',
      'c) 20',
      'd) 4',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question : '9. What is top 1 browser app 2024?',
    correctAnswerIndex : 0,
    options: [
      'a) Firefox',
      'b) Google Chrome',
      'c) Microsoft Edge',
      'd) Apple Safari',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question : '10. What grade I should get?',
    correctAnswerIndex : 0,
    options: [
      'a) A',
      'b) B',
      'c) C',
      'd) D',
    ],
  ),
];